{"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the anime Initial D, how does Takumi Fujiwara describe a drift?", "correct_answer": "&#039;. . . the front tires slide so the car won&#039;t face the inside&#039;", "incorrect_answers": ["&#039;. . . the wheels lose traction, making the car slide sideways&#039;", "&#039;. . . the car oversteers through a curve, causing it to turn faster&#039;", "&#039;. . . you turn a lot&#039;"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the anime, &quot;Full Metal Panel&quot;, who is Kaname&#039;s best friend?", "correct_answer": "Kyoko Tokiwa", "incorrect_answers": ["Melissa Mao", "Ren Mikihara", "Teletha &quot;Tessa&quot; Testarossa"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In &quot;Highschool of the Dead&quot;, where did Komuro and Saeko establish to meet after the bus explosion?", "correct_answer": "Eastern Police Station", "incorrect_answers": ["The Center Mall", "Komuro&#039;s House", "On The Main Bridge"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Which of the following countries does &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure: Stardust Crusaders&quot; not take place in?", "correct_answer": "Philippines", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Pakistan", "Egypt"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "What year was &quot;JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure: Phantom Blood&quot; first released?", "correct_answer": "1987", "incorrect_answers": ["2013", "1983", "1995"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "What is the last line muttered in the anime film &quot;The End of Evangelion&quot;?", "correct_answer": "&quot;How disgusting.&quot;", "incorrect_answers": ["&quot;Idiot, I won&#039;t let you kill me!&quot;", "&quot;Nothing.&quot;", "&quot;Goddammit, Shinji.&quot;"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Winch of these names are not a character of JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure?", "correct_answer": "JoJo Kikasu", "incorrect_answers": ["Jean-Pierre Polnareff", "George Joestar", "Risotto Nero"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Which of these anime have over 7,500 episodes?", "correct_answer": "Sazae-san", "incorrect_answers": ["Naruto", "One Piece", "Chibi Maruko-chan"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "multiple", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Which song was the callsign for Stefan Verdemann&#039;s KWFM radio station in Urasawa Naoki&#039;s &quot;Monster&quot;?", "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["What a Wonderful World", "When You Wish Upon A Star", "Singing In The Rain"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}